SOLD OUT ON YOU
Hae-seok.
I just double-checked the ingredient list,
and the allergen content was missing.
Oh, sorry.
The labeling rules change often,
so you have to be extra careful
when making the list.
When I checked…
Oh, Chang-ho's picking on his junior.
Hey, do you want me
to squeeze your mouth shut?
No, wait. I shouldn't mess with your face.
Right. That would be cruel.
Don't be so mean.
Aren't you guys hungry?
How about tofu and kimchi?
-Sure!
-Yeah!
I have to finish this first.
Hang on. How about some makgeolli too?
-I'd love that.
-Sounds great.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on.
There won't be any seats.
If I go, there will be.
Calm down. Let's talk this out.
You should've at least
heard Woo-su out to the end.
Heard out what?
His stupid rambling about responsibility
and conscience and all that?
So you didn't change.
This is who you've always been.
Hae-seok, without me,
The Usu
would've gone under
before you even joined.
You guys were able
to do research comfortably,
without worrying about a thing,
thanks to me.
I brought in all the development funding.
But that jerk Choi Woo-su…
abandoned me.
Do you have any idea how I felt?
And I haven't told Chang-ho yet…
Yes?
…but I'd like you to be the team leader.
What did you just say?
Our new project.
THE USU
NEW PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT PROPOSAL
I want you to be in charge.
Woo-su, the team leader
should be Chang-ho.
He has much more experience than me,
and he understands--
You're right.
Chang-ho looks at the bigger picture,
while you focus on the details.
But right now,
I need a researcher
who values the small factors.
Chang-ho keeps insisting
we go mass-market,
but honestly, it kind of bothers me.
It feels like an excuse
to leave someone behind.
You pathetic loser.
Stop making excuses.
What happened to The Usu
was all Woo-su's fault!
Mechoori.
What are you doing out here in the cold?
Why don't we walk a bit?
FINAL EPISODE
Good job.
I'm saying that to the both of us.
I think we deserve to hear that.
If there's anything you wanted to say,
you can say it now.
Let's get everything off our chests
before going home.
There's nothing left to get off my chest.
I've said everything I needed to say.
After the incident five years ago,
I went to a bus terminal
and just took the next bus
that was leaving.
Then I got off somewhere
I didn't even know
and…
kept walking aimlessly.
That's how I ended up in Deokpung Village.
Now that I think about it,
I guess Woo-su
led me to Deokpung Village.
I'm glad…
that Woo-su was the friend…
I used to know.
Hey, lean on me.
Come on.
This is uncomfortable.
Then I'll stand like this.
DAM YE-JIN, JI YUN-JI
The Good Morning Cream incident shook
the cosmetics industry five years ago,
leaving numerous victims harmed
by the toxic ingredients in the product.
The case was closed
after CEO Choi Woo-su took his own life.
But today, that truth
was overturned with a confession.
The home shopping host Ji Yun-ji
made a public confession
-about Good Morning Cream…
-It was Ji Yun-ji?
Dam Ye-jin must have been so upset.
Did you know about this?
-No, I had no idea.
-Gosh…
She admitted
that she had kept quiet about it.
What's more, CEO Son Chang-ho
obtained the list of testers
for Noori Cream and bribed them
into claiming false damages.
After being threatened by Son Chang-ho,
Ji Yun-ji eventually confessed the truth.
The police have secured voice recordings
and launched an investigation.
The person you are calling is unavailable…
Here's your coffee.
Geez, that's hot!
I told you to get me hot coffee
with a cool first sip.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Damn it…
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Mr. Cha just barely managed
to get the temperature right.
Geez…
SON CHANG-HO
Should I take care of him?
Make sure it doesn't blow back on me.
I'm going to finish this and go home.
Wrap things up here
and book my flight back.
What about Mr. Seo, ma'am?
You said Mr. Cha
took my dashcam memory card, right?
We should take care
of the factory manager before I go.
Yes, ma'am.
This is my chance
to make an impression on her.
Oh, gosh…
Avalokiteshvara.
Mr. Seo…
Father.
All I did was do as Ms. Michelle ordered.
I did receive a lot of money,
but I was on the run.
I didn't even get to buy anything.
God loves you.
Then will I be forgiven?
If you confess your sins
at the police station, not here.
Mr. Seo…
You startled me,
disappearing off like that.
Darn it.
And so the Lord has already forgiven you.
Hold hands with those beside you
and pray before the Lord.
Oh, Lord!
JOONG-HOON AND ERIC WERE HERE
It contains recordings of Ms. Michelle
ordering that microbes
be added to the essence.
I'll go to the police and turn myself in,
so let's never cross paths again.
Shall I proceed?
Yes.
Darn it.
Gosh. Why would you eat that?
Michelle Desruets, deputy CEO
of the global skincare brand L'Étoile
and potential heir to the group,
has been accused of criminal acts
during a power struggle
over the group's succession.
Deputy CEO Michelle was found
to have bribed a factory manager
and ordered microbes to be added
to the essence planned for launch in Korea
in an attempt to stop Executive Director
Eric Seo's entry into the market.
Happy now?
Michelle.
Stop pretending to be so innocent.
It's all over now anyway.
We…
weren't like this from the start.
When we first became a family,
you showed me the world.
You protected me from kids
who made fun of my eye color.
Don't fool yourself.
I've never liked you.
If you felt that I did,
that's only because Father
gave me a compliment
whenever I took care of you.
Ever since you and your mom
barged into my life,
I've been miserable every single day.
I even had to share
the few words I barely managed…
to exchange with Father.
I just…
wanted him to love me like he used to.
I'll pretend I didn't hear
that you never liked me.
At least in my memories,
you treated me the same,
whether Father was around or not.
COMPLAINT
L'ÉTOILE DEPUTY CEO MICHELLE
I need you to do something for me.
What's that?
Darn it!
Sir, move back!
It must be your first time here.
This is a one-way street.
Yeah, whatever.
Where's the mushroom farm?
Why do you ask?
If you don't know, then get lost!
Move!
We're busy, you punk!
Geez.
What?
No…
Mechoori…
You're here.
Wow, are these the mushrooms?
It looks so strange.
Who are you?
You don't need to know.
If you just get lost,
I won't hurt your pretty face.
If things don't go his way,
he'll resort to anything, even violence.
Get out.
Get out?
We just have to get rid of this.
Move!
Don't stand around. Finish up in ten.
-Yes, boss.
No… Stop!
Hey, what's with you?
-Don't strain yourself.
-Hey!
Who are you?
If you touch a single hair on him,
you're all dead.
Mu-won!
Mr. Kang!
Get him!
Please pick up.
-What is this?
-What the hell?
You shouldn't play dirty like that.
Mr. Park.
Mechoori, leave the rest to us.
-Yeah.
-Leave it to us.
Gosh…
Hey, move.
Move over.
What kind of group is this?
Hey, you're alive.
Geez.
Did I not tell you it's a one-way street?
In Deokpung, you get punished
for not sticking to the rules.
That's right.
Whatever. Shut up.
Hey!
-Get them!
-Let's go!
Come on!
Where'd that woman go?
Are you all right?
What a lunatic.
You jerk!
Darn it!
Stop!
What happened to my voice? Hey!
That hurt! What the heck?
Hey! Come here, you punk.
You jerk!
Hey! Fall back!
How dare you!
Everyone, get up.
That street is the way out.
Understand?
Go on.
The roads are dark here.
Hurry up and leave.
We did it!
-We did it!
We did it…
Hey! Be quiet.
Hey, what's that bus?
This is a one-way street!
Where are you going?
Do you want some corn?
Damn it!
Pull yourself together!
The others should move back.
Hurry up and reverse!
Hey, move!
Damn it…
Kwang-mo, take a look at him.
You'll have to keep an eye on him.
I don't think I was wrong.
Still, I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm the one
who made you like this. I'm sorry.
I'M SORRY, THIS IS ALL MY FAULT
Chang-ho!
Chang-ho…
Why did you come here?
This only makes me more miserable.
Chang-ho, don't do this.
Just come down. Let's talk.
It's over.
Chang-ho, it's okay.
Everything's okay, so just come down.
I understand how you feel--
No, you don't.
Chang-ho!
Why did you do it, then?
Why…
Just live.
You have to live.
You should live and apologize,
and take responsibility.
Chang-ho.
Let's go back together.
Chang-ho…
-We did it!
-Finally!
-We finally did it!
Chang-ho!
Mechoori…
I'm sorry.
Mechoori!
-Who are you?
-Sorry.
-Where…
-Ms. Dam?
Mechoori…
What--
I was so scared!
What is it? Did that hurt?
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
Fooled…
Fooled you.
Seriously.
Cut it out.
I really got hurt here.
Really? Where? Let me see--
Oh, gosh! I'm so sorry.
Oh, no. I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Sorry…
Mr. Kang.
Ms. Moon.
Are you all right?
Do you have any idea how worried I was?
Ms. Moon.
My dear Ae-ra…
Ae-ra,
you're really strong.
Should we take him to a bigger hospital?
There's nothing else I can do.
Right.
Oh, gosh.
Mechoori! You're here!
What are you all doing here?
We have to fix this place up
for you to make that cream.
-That's right.
-These are precious mushrooms.
Yeah, they're our village treasures.
Of course. Let's all do our best
and clean this up.
Come over after you're done.
I'll boil some meat for everyone.
Let's have makgeolli with it.
Now we're talking!
Mr. Son Chang-ho, do you admit
that you hired thugs
to break into the mushroom farm
and damage the facilities?
Yes.
Woo-su.
THE LATE CHOI WOO-SU
I'm here.
I'm sorry…
I took so long.
Woo-su.
We're going to succeed this time,
for all of us.
So watch over us.
HIT HOMESHOPPING
We're doing the Noori Cream broadcast
as planned, in two weeks.
So do your best.
All right. Thank you.
Do you know that the Good Morning Cream
incident broke out
as soon as I was appointed director?
And my first decision as the director
was to ignore the executives
who wanted you dismissed.
That means you, Dam Ye-jin,
are Dong Hyun-ki's HIT.
This isn't encouragement. It's pressure.
So, did you and your mother make up?
What?
Song Myeong-hwa's the only one
who could've convinced Ji Yun-ji.
She must have mentioned you.
Yun-ji has a daughter too.
Song Myeong-hwa's full of pride,
but she's actually a coward.
Why don't you reach out to her first?
Please, sit.
Ms. Ji.
Why are you giving this to me?
Ask your mother.
I heard Noori Cream was confirmed
for your broadcast.
Why did you ask to see me?
I wanted to ask you a favor.
What?
Let's do the Noori Cream launch
at the mushroom farm.
But then we'll have to pull
the staff out for an entire day.
Would that be possible?
Of course not.
Plus, it's our first broadcast.
Let's just do it safely at our studio.
Please.
Ms. Eom. Mr. Hwang.
Why? Let's hear the reason first.
You both know
that there's a story behind the materials
for the Noori Cream.
So?
Sincerity.
That farm can explain Noori Cream
without me having to say anything.
Should I arrange outsourced staff?
Mr. Hwang.
Go to the farm tomorrow
and check the camera paths.
All right.
My lifespan is shortening by the day.
You know I love you two, right?
What are those?
You're going to get even busier now,
so I wanted to give you
some healthy snacks.
Where were you hiding those?
Goodness! How did you know I love these?
These are my favorite flavors.
I knew it.
Ms. Eom, have this and calm down a bit.
This is good.
I'm letting it slide for this.
Great work, guys. Cheers.
-Cheers!
-I just realized something.
-What?
The best appetizer
is an eight-hour meeting.
This tastes so good. It's insane.
Let me pour you a glass.
I'm sorry, Sung-mi.
Right.
I'm sorry, Mr. Hwang.
I'm just grateful
that I can have a drink with Ye-jin.
I mean it.
-Sung-mi.
-I can't believe it.
Me too.
I love drinking with you.
Are you sure you can get home safely?
Hey, I have someone to pick me up.
Me too.
He'll come running right away.
Mr. Proper?
Yes.
Are you drunk?
There's no way he can come here.
Hey, that's what I should say.
How could Mr. Park come here at this hour?
My honey potato will fly over
from Deokpung
-as soon as I say I miss him.
-My Mechoori
is always waiting for me,
even at 3:00 a.m.
-Don't be silly.
-Should we make a bet?
On who comes first?
Fine.
And if you lose?
Everything's on me.
-Okay! Mr. Hwang, you join too.
-You too.
But I don't have a girlfriend.
Call someone you can trust.
Let's do this.
We have to call at the same time.
She's ready. Mr. Hwang, come on.
Get ready, set…
-Go!
Mechoori, where are you right now?
Honey potato, what are you doing?
I miss you.
Owner of the car with plate 1040?
Why aren't they picking up?
Hey, babe.
Sorry.
My girlfriend's here. I'll get going.
-I've been calling you nonstop.
-Right.
-I'm so sorry…
-You'll be charged extra.
Should we split the bill?
-Shall we?
-Let's split it.
Can you move that to the side
so they won't overlap?
Move the table over here, please.
Mr. Hwang, over there and there.
-Please be careful.
-Yes, we'll make sure of it.
Stay still.
-Come on. Stay still.
-What are you doing?
Mr. Park.
Ms. Eom.
Well, I…
HAVE SOME SNACKS, EVERYONE
We're here from Moon Cafe.
Have some coffee!
Have some coffee, everyone!
Delicious coffee
made by an amazing barista.
-Have some coffee.
-Stop it…
-Here you go.
-Have some macarons.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
Hello.
Mr. Kang's really generous with his money.
It's cool.
Tomato.
Did you just call another man "cool"?
I just meant he's quite generous.
That's all.
No, not there. More to the left.
Please keep supporting Moon Cafe.
You did great today.
Thank you for helping me.
No problem.
Ms. Moon,
I'll go and help move
some heavy stuff over there.
Sure.
Hang on.
I can carry it.
Don't worry. Go on.
Wait, be careful.
We should carry it together…
A man should work with his body,
not just his wallet.
-Body?
-Yes.
This is a body built through exercise.
Are you sure? It doesn't seem like it.
Mr. Park, how old are you exactly?
Hey, we're the same age.
What month? I'm September.
I was born in March.
I guess you were a little kid, Mu-won.
A little kid?
Let's settle this!
That's just what I wanted.
Ms. Ae-ra,
do you want to go and watch?
"Ms. Ae-ra"?
I was born in 1989.
I am older than you.
This is going to be fun. Let's go.
You're so cool!
INSANE AURA, DON'T GIVE UP
Relying on all your gear?
Go, Kwang-mo!
You're so cool!
Ms. Moon!
Yes!
I feel like I'm the one who lost
after seeing him do that.
I'm sorry I suggested this.
DEOKPUNG YOUTH CENTER
KWANG-MO
SUNG-MI
My tomato!
Where are you going?
Did you see that?
How about some hot cappuccino?
Cappuccino?
Aren't you having lunch?
You peeked, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
DAM YE-JIN'S ONLY1
NOORI CREAM LAUNCH BROADCAST D-DAY
Starting today, I'll be meeting you
every Saturday at this hour
with Dam Ye-jin's Only1.
I'm your host, Dam Ye-jin.
You must be wondering
what all this greenery is.
This is the white flower
noori mushroom farm
that produces the main ingredients
for the Noori Cream.
To celebrate our launch for Noori Cream,
we invited a special guest,
the nation's first love,
Actress Song Myeong-hwa.
Hello. I'm Song Myeong-hwa.
Will you join the Noori Cream
launch broadcast as a guest?
Our customers are already going crazy
over your appearance.
"The goddess is here." "It feels
like our TV quality has improved."
Seeing you in person,
I can tell that your skin is flawless.
I put in a lot of effort.
But my skin condition today
is all thanks to Noori Cream.
It hasn't even been a week
since I started using it,
but people have been asking me
about my skincare process.
I only made one change.
Using this Noori Cream.
I've used dozens
of different creams before,
but I've never used a cream
with such a soft texture.
Right. One thing I'd like everyone
to experience for themselves
is the texture.
Everyone, if you look here,
you can see how it gets absorbed
just with a few light swipes.
The reason why this texture was made
is because the researcher of Gojeuneok Bio
wanted to minimize irritation,
even while applying the cream,
for users with sensitive skin.
That's why there's no irritation at all.
-It's very mild.
-That's right.
But that doesn't mean it just evaporates.
As soon as you apply it,
it feels light but still rich.
Right? And that's because
it contains the maximum amount
of this new ingredient from the mushroom
that strengthens your skin barrier.
If you look at the clinical results
displayed on the screen,
this is the result
just after two weeks of use.
I know that many of you
are concerned about your skin.
Noori Cream was created
precisely for those
who had trouble finding a cream
they could use
without any skin irritation.
The main benefit of this cream
is that it helps
all skin types, no matter how sensitive.
CEO Lee Hae-seok's
sincerity and dedication
is contained in this cream.
Human testing is just the bare minimum.
What matters the most
is how your skin changes
after applying this cream.
That's why we're offering samples
with confidence.
You can try it yourself and decide.
Viewer 0827, you said you bought it
since you believed
it would be safe for your child
with skin problems.
Everyone, today's stock
is completely sold out.
Thank you all for showing
your love and support.
Thank you.
-Great job.
-You did great.
Good job.
-Great work, everyone.
-Great job.
-We did it!
-Good job!
You said you had something to say.
I have no idea how to start
untangling this mess.
Did you…
really believe that I wanted…
to get revenge?
Ye-jin.
Back then, I was young and selfish.
I didn't know what was truly important.
I know I don't have the right to say this,
but don't resent your father.
He really did his best
to stop you from getting hurt.
I hurt you…
and him…
in so many ways.
I'm…
sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Ye-jin.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
YOUR HEALTH IS THE MOST IMPORTANT
MAKE SURE TO EAT WELL
YE-JIN, I DROPPED BY
DON'T SKIP YOUR MEALS
TELL ME IF YOU WANT TO EAT ANYTHING
SONGHYEON MARKET
How did you make the time?
I just…
wanted to eat your cooking.
Then I should show off my skills today.
Sir, the one on the right looks better.
-All right.
-Okay. I'll get that one.
How about grilled pork neck?
Sounds great.
I'll get some pork neck too.
Ma'am!
Oh, my. Is it you, Ye-jin?
How have you been?
I loved the rice cakes here.
Should we get one?
Yes.
We'll take this.
Thanks.
It's really good.
Eat up.
Dad.
Why aren't you asking anything?
You saw the broadcast.
Because I feel bad.
Don't say that.
You're always saying you're sorry.
I…
I'm sorry about everything.
played dumb all this time.
I wanted you to feel hurt
because…
you hurt me first.
But I shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry…
Dad.
No, don't say that.
You don't have to apologize.
But…
are my side dishes salty?
-What?
-Is that why you didn't eat them?
No, it's just that Mechoori
prefers really bland food.
Right?
Yes.
That's a relief.
Were you worried about that all this time?
Yes. I was.
Today, we'll be making dumpling soup
with a rich broth
made from beef bones.
Has anyone here
tried making dumplings by hand?
Just one?
Today's class won't be easy, then.
You're working quite hard.
I want to make some for my daughter,
but this is pretty hard.
REVIEWS
Are you nervous?
You do it.
No, you do it.
Let's do it together.
Click on the count of three.
One, two.
Three!
EVERYONE, HURRY UP AND BUY THIS
ONLY USING THIS NOW
MY SKIN IMPROVED SO MUCH
THIS IS INSANE!
WHY DIDN'T YOU MAKE THIS SOONER?
THANK YOU FOR MAKING THIS
KEEP MAKING PRODUCTS LIKE THIS
BEST CHOICE OF MY LIFE
SLEEPING PILLS
As for this product,
popular idols are all
using this these days.
It's been going viral.
Try it.
Hey, the color's nice.
There were a lot of options.
That's right.
It's really pretty.
And this color is known
to be used by male idols.
That's great. We need products like that.
This is nice.
Yes?
Hey, Jin-yi.
Hello!
Welcome!
I'm Na Jin-yi,
who will be joining Dam Ye-jin's Only1
as an assistant host.
Nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you, Jin-yi.
Let's do this.
Okay.
-Babe.
-Yes?
I want this one.
I'll buy it for you.
I love you, babe.
Hey!
Ae-ra…
What?
How dare you show your face here?
Ms. Moon.
Wait just a moment.
Ms. Pang.
It's been a while. It's me, Kang Mu-won.
Oh, Mr. Kang. How are you?
I'm great. Can I talk to you for a moment?
Marriage fraud?
Are you sure?
No, that's not true!
Who are you?
Losers like you
would never know how valuable
Ms. Moon's affection is.
It's worth much more
than your clothes and accessories.
Hey! Take off everything I gave you.
No, wait…
Stop that! You old woman!
Old woman? You jerk!
You!
You spineless jerk!
That hurts!
You're dead!
Please call the cops!
Cops?
-Call the cops!
-No, wait! Don't!
Is that really Park Kwang-mo?
He looks more handsome in person.
Should I go and say hi?
Excuse me.
Are you Park Kwang-mo
of "Park Kwang-mo TV"?
Well, I can't say I'm not.
Could we have a handshake?
Of course.
I'm Park Kwang-mo from Deokpung Village.
-Me too.
-You must be my subscribers.
We are!
Hello.
She seems a little off.
-Bye.
-Have a nice day.
Have a nice day.
Wow…
Should I just delete your channel?
You know, it kind of bothers me
now that the whole world
knows how cute you are.
Come on.
My cherry tomato
is the only one who looks cute to me.
Close your eyes.
Open them.
PARK KWANG-MO TV
100,000 SUBS
What is this?
Park Kwang-mo.
I'll help you get a Gold Play Button
within a year.
So let's live together.
Tomato…
Then will you live in Deokpung Village?
Come on!
That's not the point right now.
I finally made you
a birthday meal, Bong-chan.
Happy birthday.
Sir,
another magazine meeting
has been scheduled for tomorrow evening.
What? As soon as I arrive in France?
Yes.
It's the same here and there.
Everyone's really interested
in the new CEO.
I made a list of some potential questions.
Where is it?
Are you sad to go?
No.
I probably won't be back for a long time.
I learned a lot of things here.
We're going to be very busy now.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir.
It showed excellent regenerative effects
when used with Noori Cream.
But this is the first sample, right?
This will sell even better than the cream.
-Right?
-Yes.
It's all good, but…
Oh, please…
Seriously. Everything's perfect.
But with serums,
absorption is really important.
If it doesn't absorb well,
the cream you use afterward won't sink in.
The texture is very refreshing and nice,
but the absorption is a little lacking.
-Ms. Dam.
-Yes?
You're just impatient.
Look.
If you just pat it a few times,
it gets absorbed.
Many of our customers are in a hurry
before going to work.
If you add a substance
that improves absorption,
I think it'll get a much better response.
Don't you think?
Look.
The Noori Serum
was made with fermented ingredients
to increase absorption.
If we add synthetic ingredients,
it would disrupt the formula
and reduce its effectiveness.
Ms. Dam, are you suggesting
that we lower its effectiveness?
Mr. Lee, you know that's not what I mean.
Then what did you mean, Ms. Dam?
-Should we stop them?
-I'm the main host, you know.
-It's just a discussion.
-I'm the one communicating with customers.
Just continue what you were doing.
There's the saying,
"What comes around goes around."
-Don't you know that?
-No.
I think you mean,
"What goes around comes around."
DO YOU WANT TO GO EAT MALATANG?
-Don't you know Newton's third law?
-No, I don't.
Absorption is key for serums.
HONEY POTATO
SEE YOU SOON
-Geez. You're the one who…
-What?
Okay. I'm sorry.
-Hey!
-"Hey"?
Sorry…
-Ms. Dam Ye-jin!
-Yes, Mechoori!
It's Matthew Lee.
LEE HAE-SEOK (MECHOORI)
Geez…
We should just communicate
by email from now on.
You're always nitpicking
at whatever I say.
I actually did a lot of research
to come up with that suggestion.
Three times.
What?
WEEKEND RULES
IF YOU BRING UP WORK, YOU HAVE TO KISS
You talked about work three times,
so you owe me three kisses.
-We're in the yard.
-The yard is part of my house.
-That's not fair.
-Yes, it is.
Come on. Three kisses.
No.
Hey, that's the rule! Number three.
Okay, fine.
So this is how you want to play it?
-Wait!
-Come here.
Get over here.
Wait.
Okay.
Hang on.
I really need to get this straight.
What?
When did you start liking me?
I'm not sure.
Come on. Think.
When should we say we started dating?
Is that important?
Hey, Mr. Lee.
Tell me exactly
when you started liking me.
Som-yi told me
that if I start wondering
whether someone slept well and ate well,
that's when I've become a fan.
I guess it's when I started
worrying about
whether you slept well or not.
That's nice.
So, were there any lines
in this book that spoke to you?
Well, there was a line here
that said modern science
still hasn't discovered
a better stabilizer than kind words.
Thank you for today.
Me too.
DEOKPUNG COMMUNITY CENTER
See you tomorrow.
Make sure to sleep under your covers.
It's cold at night.
SEO JIN-WON AS JEON WON-TAEK
YANG HEUNG-JU AS SO JONG-IL
Mother. Ma'am.
You're the best.
I'll be back next time.
JUNG SU-JIN, LEE SAEROMI AS WIVES
Take care of your health.
KIM JUNG-HWAN AS JEON JUNG-MUK
I'll buy you dinner tomorrow.
What?
Let's have dinner tomorrow.
YOON JAE-CHAN AS HWANG KI-HONG
Look at you.
Som-yi, hurry up and go to bed.
I'm going.
AHN SE-BIN AS NA SOM-YI
KIM SEO-AN AS NA JIN-YI
Mom, I'm sleepy.
You're sleepy?
-Mom.
-Yes?
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Seo-a.
-I love you.
PARK AH-IN AS JI YUN-JI
Good work today.
I look forward to working with you.
SHIN DONG-MI AS DIRECTOR DONG
I'll do better tomorrow.
You already did well today.
WOO HEE-JIN AS SONG MYEONG-HWA
KIM YOUNG-JAE AS DAM SEOK-GYEONG
You did great today.
I'll love you even more tomorrow.
JO BOK-RAE AS PARK KWANG-MO
PARK YE-YOUNG AS EOM SUNG-MI
When will we meet each other's parents?
-What?
-The coffee's great.
Your cappuccino is delicious.
This is really tasty.
And it's decaf, so I can still sleep well.
JO WOO-RI AS MOON AE-RA
YOON BYUNG-HEE AS KANG MU-WON
I'll meet you in my dream.
GOH DOO-SHIM AS YANG SANG-GEUM
I feel a bit sad having to leave.
You did a great job today.
KIM JOONG-DON AS CHA JOONG-HOON
Then, au revoir.
KIM BUM AS ERIC SEO
"Matthew was no longer alone,
and he lived happily with his friends."
The end.
Som-yi gave this to me as a gift.
So he's Mechoori.
It's Matthew Lee.
Goodnight.
Sleep well.
CHAE WON-BEEN AS DAM YE-JIN
AHN HYO-SEOP AS LEE HAE-SEOK
SOLD OUT ON YOU
THANKS TO SPECIAL GUESTS
AHN SANG-WOO AND SEO HYUN-WOO
THE VILLAINS WHO NEVER MADE THE ENDING
OK JA-YEON AS MICHELLE
CHAE DONG-HYUN AS SON CHANG-HO
JO WAN-GI AS FACTORY MANAGER
EUN SUN-WOO AS SECRETARY SHIN
SPECIAL GUESTS
SEO HYUN-WOO, PARK JI-HWAN, AHN SANG-WOO
NOH SEONG-EUN AS BONG-CHAN
KOH SEO-HEE AS YOUNG YANG SANG-GEUM
JO JIN-HYEONG AS GI-BOK
NAM GWON-A AS MS. OKPO
JANG EUN-SIL AS GI-SUN
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park